# CHRISTOPHER, ESUMOBI WISDOM

## IT Specialist

Port Harcourt, Nigeria

★ themainchris@gmail.com

twitter.com/EsChris1

+2348136624672 f chris.wisdom.1000 Chrismobi2022



#### **Profile**

A developer and an IT Specialist with over 6 years of experience. I Diagnose, troubleshoot and resolve a range of software, hardware and connectivity issues, provides customer service support by performing detailed investigation of customer service complaints and issues. An experienced ICT tutor.

#### **Education/Certificates**

2022 2017-2018 2012 - 2016	Developer, ElanHub ITF/NACA, Port Harcourt, Rivers State Project Manager, Institute of Arts Management & Professionals, Calabar B.Sc. Geography, University of Nigeria, Nsukka
2008 - 2009	Diploma in Computer Science, Great Computer and Communication
2001 - 2007	Institute, PH  NECO, Saint George's Grammar School, Obinomba, Delta State.

#### **Professional Experience**

2015 - 2016	GIS Lab Assistant, University of Nigeria, Nsukka
2016 - 2017	ICT Teacher, Our Lady of Apostles School, Obiaruku, Delta State
2017 - 2018	Graphic Designer, Klint IT Center, Calabar
2019 - 2020	Sotfware Manager, Karis Media, GRA, Port Harcourt
2021 - 2022	ICT Tutor, Excellent Montessori School, Port Harcourt
2021 - 2022	Videographer/Video Editor, Artful Media, Port Harcourt

#### Other Certificates

- Project Management Professional (PMP), Institute of Arts Management and Professional Studies (IAMPS).
- NYSC Specialized Skills Acquisition Program in ICT

#### **Technical Skills**

### **Programming** Languages

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Python
- **JavaScript**

#### **Others**

- CorelDraw
- Microsoft PowerPoint
- Adobe Premier Pro
- Microsoft Word
- MS Excel, & other range of software.

**Interpersonal Skills** 

- Good Communication
- Emotionally intelligent Problem solving &

decision making

- Team-work
- Professional Instructor

#### References

Pst. Levi Jeremiah, Lead Pastor, Charisma Embassy In't, Choba, Port-Harcourt, Rivers State. 08065232764

Mr. Chinedu Ogbodo, GIS Lecturer, UNN 08036547912